M: +91-8181814380

SHUBHAM PATEL

Operations | Logistics | Reporting

CAREER OBJECTIVE:

Seeking a challenging career in operations management. Excel in operations and supply chain management and further self equip to face various challenges in the industry.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

7 years of work experience in Technical Operations in logistics industry, with strong operational support knowledge in the Public Sector Natural propensity for analytical thinking, exceptional numeracy and problem-solving skills, and advanced knowledge of tools and techniques for delivering with a strong focus on business process improvement. Well-developed communication and interpersonal skills; demonstrated track record of building and leading high performing teams; ability to develop and manage relationships across all levels of stakeholders.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Applications : Microsoft Office Suite – Excel- Advanced level

Management Tools : TULEAP, GPS Monitoring, WPS

Concepts : E-tendering, Data Analysis- Excel, Dashboard preparation

WORK HISTORY:

Technical Support Officer

Minda i-Connect Pvt Ltd.

Uttar Pradesh Food and Civil Supply Department of India

(April 2019 - Present)

- ✓ Monitor & Data Management GPS Dashboard for Food department, Uttar Pradesh.
- ✓ Prepare reports and submit analysis on various alerts
- ✓ Categorize various issues and submit weekly and monthly report
- ✓ Analyze transporter run distance with actual distance and submit spend reports
- ✓ Functional consultant in preparation of mobile app for GPS data gathering and mobile app support
- ✓ Command and Control center management for the food department.
- ✓ Tender evaluation- Technical and Financial- Prepare excel reports and support senior staff

Customer Support Executive

Shah Tower Pvt. Limited, Lucknow

(July 2016 - August 2016)

- ✓ Customer support for AIRCEL client
- ✓ Attend and monitor incoming technical calls.
- ✓ Submit calls history and call related issues to reporting officer
- ✓ Monitor various types of issues and highlight various alerts to reporting officer.

State Planning Department

Yojana Bhawan (U.P. Sachivalaya)

(November 2014 - March 2016)

- ✓ Operating Computer Work
- ✓ E-mailing And Printing Setup Officers Data

Customer Help Line (Food & Civil Supply Department)

Food and Civil Supply Department of India Uttar Pradesh

(January 2018 - April 2019)

- ✓ Customer support for Ration Card Holders and grievance redressal.
- ✓ Submit calls history and call related issues to the reporting officer.

EDUCATIONAL CREDENTIALS:

- ✓ 10th Class Passed From U.P. Board in 2009 with 2nd Division
- ✓ 12th Class Passed From U.P. Board in 2011 with 2nd Division.
- ✓ Graduation (B.A.) Complete from k.k.v (Lucknow University in 2014).

COUMPUTER DIPLOMA

- ✓ ADCA.
- ✓ CCC Diploma from NIELIT

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father Name : Jang Bahadur Date of Birth : 05-06-1994

Email : <u>Shubhamverama12@gmail.com</u>

Mobile no : +91 8181814380 Current Location : Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh

Languages known : English, Hindi,

DECLARATION:

I, Shubham Patel hereby declare that the information contained here is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place: Lucknow

Date: (SHUBHAM PATEL)